convertuum.com 2017-12-15

# Convertuum

The following Privacy Policy of DoubleDigital Ltd. (hereinafter cited as “Company”) states and describes the rights of Publishers and Advertisers (hereinafter called as “you” or “your”) who access and/or use the Convertuum website (further on cited as “website”, “we”, “us” or “our”) and all related services, applications, and tools. It concerns, without limitation, the use, collection, storage, sharing and protection of the personal and non-personal information by the Company.

This Privacy Policy is provided to you as the ground for making an informed decision as to the onward website use. The Company has the right to update this Privacy Policy from time to time, and the updates made come into effect immediately once posted. It is crucially important to periodically read through this Privacy Policy.

## Collection of Information

The Company collects both personal and non-personal information via online forms, surveys, phone calls, and other means of communication.

## A. Personally Identifiable Information

We may collect from time to time such personal information from you as name, postal and email addresses, zip/postal code, phone numbers (wireless as well), gender, birth date, education, marital status, salary range, social security number, interests, employment information, and any other data.

## B. Non-Personally Identifiable Information

This refers to all information, without limitation, that concerns the use of computer systems needed to access the website, namely the date and time of your visit, IP address, domain, your activity, etc.

## C. Cookies and Web Beacons

We may use Cookies, Web Beacons and/or Similar Technologies to weigh the Internet-related information regarding your access and usage with information stored in our database. This is necessary to ensure the security of your account and eliminate the risk of fraud across the website and services.

Cookies are small files with data from your web browser that is stored while you are using the website. When you access the website, your browser notifies the website of your previous activity by sending the cookie back to the server.

A Web Beacon is usually a transparent graphic image or a programming code used for an image (typically 1 pixel x 1 pixel) placed on a web page. Its usage enables the website to receive and store the actions you make on the opened page that contains the web beacon.

The Company reserves the right to use similar technologies with analogous functionality and/or the ones that serve a similar purpose and bring the same results.

You retain the right to refuse our Cookies, Web Beacons, and similar technologies in case your browser or its add-ons allow you to do so, excluding the cases when Cookies, Web Beacons, and similar technologies are needed to protect you from fraud and ensure the website’s security. Keep in mind that declining our Cookies may negatively affect and interfere with your use of our website and services.

## Information Usage

The Company collects and uses information, particularly for the stated purpose to provide you with the offered service. The information may also be used to contact you and/or maybe shared with the third parties in cases when it is required to perform the service on behalf of our website, for instance, support provision to internal operations.

All your personally identifiable information will be used solely to establish the account and for communication on record keeping as required.

Your non-personally identifiable information will be used to improve the website service and for administration. We also use your log information to validate and authorize your entry to the website.

In addition, the information on your Credit Card, i.e. the card number, expiration date, etc., will be collected for financial purposes during the process and completion of transactions. Such information is disclosed only to third parties involved in such financial transactions.

## Information Disclosure

We do not disclose or share your personally identifiable information unless we provide a prior notice to you and you permit us to do so.

Your information (including identity) may be disclosed only in cases when it is required for complaint or investigation related to your website usage, or when it is necessary to contact, identify, or bring legal action against someone who interfered with our property or rights (either intended or not), or has breached the rights of website visitors or users. We have the right on a regular basis to disclose all information that we consider necessary in order to comply with the applicable regulations, law, government request or legal process. We also may disclose information in the cases determined by the requirement or permission of applicable law, which includes the exchange of such information with other organizations and companies for the purpose of fraud protection.

The Company may share the data collected by Cookies, Web Beacons and similar technologies with third parties solely in the anonymous way in the form of statistics, which do not include your personally identifiable information.

## Security

We take care of your information security by following the generally accepted standards and protect all data from an unauthorized access, disclosure, and retention. All data stored by us on our server is treated as confidential. However, you should bear in mind that despite all efforts we take to protect your data, we cannot guarantee that it is absolutely secured from any outside party that may breach it. All information you provide to us is accessed only by authorized employees.

## Privacy of Children

Our website is not developed or aimed at providing services to children. In case you think or believe that your child has shared personally identifiable data with us and you wish to remove this data from our database, please notify us at the earliest convenience.

## Third-Party Sites

Any link on our website that redirects you to a third-party site doesn’t imply our approval of that website. We have no control over the websites available via such links and do not assume any responsibility for the posted content on them. Thus, we recommend you to read the privacy policies of the linked websites before you access from our website.

## Data Transfer

In case another company takes control over our business or acquires all of the assets by means of consolidation, asset and merger transaction, or purchase, we have the right to transfer data (which includes any of your personally identifiable data provided) that we have collected from you and that is under our control to the acquiring third party.

## Consent

Your visit to our Website will state your consent as to the collection and use of any personally identifiable and/or non-personally identifiable information as noted above. In case you do not agree with any mentioned point in this Privacy Policy, please do not enter or continue using our website.

## Contacts

Feel free to contact us with any questions concerning our policy at this address: [info@convertuum.com](mailto:info@convertuum.com)
